A Guide to the Edward L. Stone/Borderland Coal Company Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Edward L. Stone Personal Papers
  - American Civic Assoc. (see also J. Horace McFarland) - correspondence about membership and activities, 1919 -1935 (Box Box 115)
  - City Planning (Zoning) - Stone was chairman of the City Planning Commission at one time. including letters, notes, minutes, proposals, and maps, 1932 (Box Box 115)
  - City Planning: Citizens Advisory Committee - correspondence, 1932 (Box Box 115)
  - City Planning - miscellaneous; notes and reprints of articles, 1932 (Box Box 115)
  - Correspondence which Miss Schilling took out of the City Planning file, 1932 (Box Box 115)
  - Stone Personal - almost exclusively personal, financial odds and ends, including a 1933 income tax return where Stone's net income is recorded at more than a half million dollars, 1932 -1935 (Box Box 115)
  - Receipts - for Stone's personal purchases, 1921, 1925; (4 folders) (Box Box 116)
  - City Planning Commission - correspondence, 1932 (Box Box 118)
  - E. L. S. Inactive - personal bank records, 1930 -1933 (Box Box 118)
  - Horace M. Engle - correspondence, 1923 -1935 (Box Box 118)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "E", 1924 -1929 (Box Box 118)
  - Presses: Kiddie Press Co. - Stone Printing information on printing presses, 1908 -1909 (Box Box 118)
  - Tours and Travel - brochures, ca. 1930 (Box Box 118)
  - Jordan-Stabler Co. - orders to this packaged food Co., 1920 -1931 (Box Box 118)
  - Huntington Valley County Club, Philadelphia - announcements, programs, invitations, newsletters, 1924 -1930 (Box Box 118)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts - invitations programs, and correspondence between Stone and this New York organization, 1923 -1928; (4 folders) (Box Box 119)
  - Edw. L. Stone - personal family correspondence, greeting cards, and Stone's resume, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 120)
  - M. F. Stone - correspondence, ca. 1916 (Box Box 120)
  - John C. Hill: weekly letters - newsletters issued by a Baltimore printer, 1924 -1932 (Box Box 122)
  - Mass. Institute of Technology - correspondence about Stone's gifts towards the establishment of a Dept. of Graphic Arts at M.I.T., and his interest therein, 1926 -1927 (Box Box 122)
  - National Industrial Conference Board - about Stone's subscription to their Bulletin, 1930 -1931 (Box Box 122)
  - Miscellaneous Virginia "A-E" - personal collection of clippings and pamphlets on various topics, including Germany's role in the war, 1915 (Box Box 123)
  - A. B. Van Buren - letters to this patron of Stone Printing, 1912 -1915 (Box Box 123)
  - Virginia - "Something About Virginia" - 1910 Census Report and a Stone Printing pamphlet about Virginia (Box Box 123)
  - U. T. A. Open Shop Division - about open shop in the printing industry, 1913 -1915 (Box Box 123)
  - Miscellaneous "V, Cn, Sj" - about ads for vacuum cleaners, motor oil, and other commercial products, 1913 (Box Box 123)
  - Virginia Iron Coal & Coke - correspondence about maintenance of Roanoke Country Club grounds, 1915 (Box Box 123)
  - Virginia Bridge & Iron Co. - Presidents report, correspondence, 1913 (Box Box 123)
  - Invoices "A-H" - about Stone's personal purchases, 1925 -1930 (Box Box 124)
  - Invoices "I-R", 1925 -1930 (Box Box 124)
  - Invoices "S-Z", 1925 -1930 (Box Box 124)
  - Rotary Club - newsletters and circulars, 1931 -1935 (Box Box 124)
  - Rotary Club - correspondence; see letter of July 11, 1932 expressing financial problems which called for Stone's resignation from the club, 1929 -1935 (Box Box 124)
  - Citizens National Bank of Baltimore - financial statements, 1907 -1909 (Box Box 125)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Roanoke, Virginia - letters, clippings and advertisements about Roanoke, 1910 -1913; (2 folders) (Box Box 125)
  - Frank Calloway - correspondence about the estate of Calloway, which Stone administered, 1911 -1912 (Box Box 125)
  - National Security League - correspondence and newsletters of this war-time citizens organization, 1917 -1913 (Box Box 126)
  - J. B. Newton - correspondence, 1918 (Box Box 126)
  - N. Y. T. (Mid Week Pictorial) - subscription information, 1919 (Box Box 126)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "N", including Norfolk & Western time tables, 1918 -1919 (Box Box 126)
  - H. C. Ogden - correspondence, 1914 (Box Box 126)
  - Parcel Post and increase postage matters - correspondence with U. T. A. over proposed postage increases, 1911 (Box Box 126)
  - J. S. Perry, Roanoke, Va. - about insurance, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 126)
  - Presbyterian Orphans' Home - brochures and correspondence, 1913 -1919 (Box Box 126)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "P", 1918 -1919 (Box Box 126)
  - Henry P. Porter - correspondence between Stone and Porter, an officer of U. T. A., 1916 -1919 (Box Box 126)
  - Roanoke Rotary Club - surveys, newsletters, 1929 -1931 (Box Box 127)
  - Benjamin Franklin Society - correspondence, announcements, invitations from this printers' association, 1922 -1931 (Box Box 127)
  - French Lick - information on this Indiana resort area, 1922 -1925 (Box Box 127)
  - The Grolier Club - announcements from this book club, 1923 -1929 (Box Box 127)
  - Receipts and bills for personal items, 1900 -1904 (Box Box 127)
  - Bills and receipts "M-Z" for personal goods, 1901 -1903 (Box Box 129)
  - Henry L. Bullen - correspondence about printing and printing exhibits, 1926 -1934 (Box Box 130)
  - Burrell Memorial Hospital - correspondence about Stone's contributions to fund raising efforts, 1919 -1933 (Box Box 130)
  - Bureau of Municipal Research, Broadway, New York letter from B. M. R. advertising its services, 1915 (Box Box 130)
  - Burke & Gregory - personal greetings and correspondence, some related to management techniques in printing, like open shop, 1914 -1932 (Box Box 130)
  - E. T. Burnett, City - correspondence about local and railroad affairs, with Burnett, purchasing agent for N. & W. Railroad, 1909 -1913 (Box Box 130)
  - Bureau of Economics - blank profit and loss statements, no date (Box Box 130)
  - Bureau of the Census - statistical data on Roanoke, 1913 -1919 (Box Box 130)
  - American Printer - correspondence about printing and rare books, 1921 -1938 (Box Box 131)
  - American Antiquarian Society - correspondence about Stone's book collecting, 1934 (Box Box 131)
  - American Red Cross - personal correspondence with its chairman, Payne, about books, 1932 -1933 (Box Box 131)
  - American Institute of Graphic Arts correspondence, announcements, invitations from this organization of which Stone was a member, 1931 -1937 (Box Box 131)
  - Peter O. Knight - president of Tampa Electric Co. and famous as a commentator on economic and political events; Stone and Knight appear to have been close friends; including letters and clippings, 1915 -1934 (Box Box 131)
  - Theodore W. Koch - letters and samples of his work from this librarian (at Northwestern), editor, and translator, 1930 -1934 (Box Box 131)
  - Correspondence "M" - miscellaneous papers about meetings, memorandums (loose notes), Michael Bakery & Mill Mountain Incline (financial statements), Mlasovsky & Wagner (tailors), Tom Moore (a railroad purchasing agent), and the Motor Vehicle Commission, 1917 -1926 (Box Box 132)
  - Correspondence "N" - about New Hotel Corp. of Roanoke, J. B. Newton, and Nurses Assoc.; see letter to architect Nolting about construction on his mountain property for idea of Stone's wealth, 1919 -1931 (Box Box 132)
  - Correspondence "O'' - correspondence with Mr. Oshima, a tour guide in Yokohama, Japan. Stone received several Japanese calendars and greeting cards from him. Oshima was injured in the 1921 earthquake and received a check from Stone to aid him in his recovery., 1916 -1931 (Box Box 132)
  - Florida (other than Royal Palm) - travel information, 1924 (Box Box 132)
  - First National Bank, Miami, Fla. - about golf clubs lost at a club that was repossessed by this bank, 1918 -1923 (Box Box 132)
  - First National Bank, Roanoke - about personal financial matters, 1916 -1924 (Box Box 132)
  - Edward L. Stone - personal notes, telegrams, valentines, and letters, almost exclusively from family members, 1899 -1915; (3 folders) (Box Box 133)
  - Edward L. Stone's statements - family budget sheets, 1915 -1916 (Box Box 133)
  - University of Virginia - University Library, etc. - some friendly correspondence about books, plus letters, clippings, and photographs related to Stone's exhibition of his library to U. Va. students., 1931 -1935 (Box Box 133)
  - Unfiled correspondence: Books - orders for books, 1936 -1937 (Box Box 134)
  - Unfiled correspondence: Carew Mfg. Co. - concerns fine paper, 1936 -1937 (Box Box 134)
  - Unfiled correspondence: Chamber of Commerce, 1936 -1937 (Box Box 134)
  - Unfiled correspondence: Jean Clough - personal letters concerning illness, health, plans for visits, and reminiscences, 1936 -1937 (Box Box 134)
  - Unfiled correspondence: Kathryn Alice Coffman - personal letters concerning illness, health, plans for visits, and reminiscences, 1936 -1937 (Box Box 134)
  - Unfiled correspondence: Mrs. Joseph Cottrell - personal letters concerning illness, health, plans for visits, and reminiscences, 1936 -1937 (Box Box 134)
  - Unfiled correspondence: Mrs. Bruce Crane - personal letters concerning illness, health, plans for visits, and reminiscences, 1936 -1937 (Box Box 134)
  - Unfiled correspondence: miscellaneous "C" - personal letters concerning illness, health, plans for visits, and reminiscences, 1936 -1937 (Box Box 134)
  - E. P. Dutton & Co. - books; concerning purchases and shipments, 1925 -1931 (Box Box 135)
  - Manufacturers Record Publishing Co. - ads for a newsletter, 1916 -1926 (Box Box 135)
  - Old Colony Club - Stone was a member of this world-wide organization of businessmen; contains ads, newsletters, and announcements, 1916 -1926 (Box Box 135)
  - Munn & Co., Washington, D. C. - letters, photos sketches, and blueprints about Stone's patent application for an interlocking R.F.D. mailbox which he invented., 1916 -1926 (Box Box 135)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "F" - chiefly with Thomas N. Fairbanks about papermaking, 1921 -1934 (Box Box 135)
  - William H. Martin, Leesburg, Va. - correspondence about the history of printing, 1924 -1932 (Box Box 135)
  - W. S. McClanahan, Roanoke, Va. - about insurance, 1920 -1935 (Box Box 135)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M", including letters with Maher about civic affairs, letters about maple sugar, and Marshall & Snellgrove (clothing store), 1919 -1927 (Box Box 135)
  - Republican Bank Note Co. - letter about an order for new checks, 1920 (Box Box 135)
  - Frank S. M. Harris - a resume, 1920 (Box Box 135)
  - 113 Literary Digest - about a subscription, 1920 (Box Box 135)
  - Miscellaneous "B" - unfiled correspondence with friends and local organizations about personal affairs, 1933; (3 folders) (Box Box 136)
  - Miscellaneous "C" - unfiled correspondence with friends and local organizations about personal affairs, 1933 (Box Box 136)
  - Congressional Representatives - bills, etc. - copies of legislation, ca. 1935 (Box Box 136)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "C", 1934 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 137)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "H", 1936 (Box Box 137)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ho-Ht", 1933 -1934 (Box Box 137)
  - American Blue Book - forms and ads, 1923 (Box Box 138)
  - American Magazine - clippings and subscriptions information, 1921 (Box Box 138)
  - American Plan - about this magazine, which Stone subscribed to, 1922 (Box Box 138)
  - Roanoke Auditorium Co. - financial information and correspondence about this investment, 1924 -1932 (Box Box 138)
  - W. F. C. Fellers - personal correspondence, especially about books, 1910 -1935 (Box Box 138)
  - To Be Filed: "A" - letters from Stone, and to him, mostly from old friends and fellow bibliophiles, written and alphabetized but never filed into the rest of the collection, 1934 -1936; (2 folders) (Box Box 139)
  - To Be Filed "B" - letters from Stone, and to him, mostly from old friends and fellow bibliophiles, written and alphabetized but never filed into the rest of the collection, 1934 -1935 (Box Box 139)
  - To Be Filed "B" - primarily business correspondence related to steel prices, book orders, magazine subscriptions, 1928 -1933; (2 folders) (Box Box 139)
  - Miss Phyllis M. Moulton - U. T. A. Librarian about archival work and books - friendly correspondence, 1924 -1925 (Box Box 140)
  - National Industrial Conference Board newsletters, yearly statements, 1932 -1934 (Box Box 140)
  - Fruits - ads and order blanks, ca. 1915 (Box Box 140)
  - Fourth American Peace Congress - Stone may have been a delegate, contains order blanks for the Congress' history, 1913 (Box Box 140)
  - 62 Ferrs Concrete Co. - about Stone's construction of buildings - ads for services, 1920 -1926 (Box Box 140)
  - Roanoke Fair Assoc. - about financial condition of Roanoke Industrial & Agricultural Assoc., 1910 -1922 (Box Box 140)
  - Roanoke Valley Co. - about another small investment interest of Stone's, 1914 -1923 (Box Box 140)
  - Roanoke Ry. & Electric Co. - about the color of Roanoke's street cars. The company appears to have been clients of Stone Printing., 1916 -1929 (Box Box 140)
  - Dr. J. Thomas Lippincott, 1433 Walnut St., Philadelphia, Penn. - a bank draft, 1917 (Box Box 140)
  - E. E. Laxman - about time cards (manufactured by Stone Printing), 1915 (Box Box 140)
  - Robert Fell and E. Lawrence - friendly correspondence; several letters about conditions at Borderland Coal (strikes, explosions, etc.), 1919 -1935 (Box Box 140)
  - James S. Russell - principal of St. Paul Normal and Industrial School to which Stone contributed, 1914 -1921 (Box Box 140)
  - Roanoke County Map - map produced by Stone Printing and correspondence about it, 1936 (Box Box 141)
  - Correspondence "Ro-Rz" - correspondence with friends about books, health, travel, 1933 -1934 (Box Box 141)
  - Correspondence "R", 1933 -1936 (Box Box 141)
  - Correspondence "Q", 1935 -1936 (Box Box 141)
  - Correspondence "P-Q", including some sketches of Richmond, 1935 -1936 (Box Box 141)
  - Miscellaneous "Pi-Pz", 1934 -1936 (Box Box 141)
  - Miscellaneous "P" - letters about economic situation of the nation, 1934 -1936 (Box Box 141)
  - Miscellaneous "K" - correspondence, invitations and announcements, 1913 -1923 (Box Box 142)
  - Fletcher Ford Co. - correspondence with this fellow printer, both friendly and professional, 1924 -1935 (Box Box 142)
  - Fleppo - a statement of assets and liabilities, 1910 (Box Box 142)
  - Miscellaneous "G" - personal correspondence with J. Gillespie, Griggs Packing, Goodyear Rubber Co. and about the Griswold Estate, 1919 -1929 (Box Box 142)
  - Miscellaneous "R" - some business, civic oriented and personal correspondence with Philip Ruxton, B. L. Robinson, and Roanoke Gas & Light, Roanoke Utilities Corp., Roanoke Travel Society, Roanoke Zinc & Lead Co., Roanoke Home Defense League, Roanoke Hardware Co., 1912 -1934 (Box Box 142)
  - Offset examples - examples of offset printing with covering letters, 1935 -1936 (Box Box 143)
  - Lucy Eugenia Osborne - letters to and from this librarian-friend in Mass., 1933 -1936 (Box Box 143)
  - Miscellaneous "O" - personal correspondence with friends, 1935 -1936 (Box Box 143)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Na" - chiefly with national organizations and magazines, 1935 -1936 (Box Box 143)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "G" - not filed into the rest of the collection, 1935 -1937 (Box Box 143)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Gl-Gz", 1934 -1937 (Box Box 143)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ga-Gr", 1934 -1937 (Box Box 143)
  - Green & Van Sant Co. - a marketing survey of Lake Lure, North Carolina, 1929 (Box Box 143)
  - Gravore Samples - ad for a transport company, no date (Box Box 143)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "F" - friendly and personal business matters handled; much has to do with philanthropies, book clubs, etc., 1935 -1937 (Box Box 143)
  - Jacques Gustave Jacquemin - a french child who Stone took on as a foster child, 1921 (Box Box 145)
  - Concrete Garage: Atlas Portland Cement Co. - inquiry into cement parking garages, 1910 (Box Box 145)
  - Mrs. Mary C. Claytor - about printing job, 1910 (Box Box 145)
  - Mrs. Corday c/o Corday & Gross Co. - letter thanking Stone for book about his company, 1900 (Box Box 145)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M", including correspondence about printing with Thomas Mecham, G. Otis Mead, McClure & Co., MacDonald & Campbell, Hugh MacRae, and Walter MacDonnell, 1914 -1931 (Box Box 146)
  - Patrick Henry Hotel - about accommodations for meetings, 1925 -1931 (Box Box 146)
  - Roanoke College - about donations, printing of catalogue, and special events, 1920 -1935 (Box Box 146)
  - Roanoke City - about civic affairs, 1922 -1928 (Box Box 146)
  - Roanoke Drug Co. - correspondence as a stockholder with company officers, 1916 -1932 (Box Box 146)
  - Roanoke Automobile Assoc. - about membership, services, disputed coverage, etc., 1919 -1931 (Box Box 146)
  - Roanoke Hospital - about donations, 1920 -1925 (Box Box 146)
  - Roanoke Water Works - Stone's correspondence as president and later as an irate customer, 1925 -1935 (Box Box 146)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "R", with C. E. Rogan, the Roanoke Cycle Co., and Arthur Rowbotham, 1920 -1934 (Box Box 146)
  - Miscellaneous "C" - personal letters to friends about visits, health, mutual interests, 1933 -1936; (2 folders) (Box Box 147)
  - Miscellaneous "Haa-Hal", 1932 -1935 (Box Box 147)
  - Miscellaneous ''Ham-Hd", 1931 -1935 (Box Box 147)
  - Miscellaneous "Hu-Hz", 1931 -1936 (Box Box 147)
  - Miscellaneous "I-J'', 1936 (Box Box 147)
  - Miscellaneous "Lo-Lz" - personal correspondence with friends about books, travel, and Stone's declining health, 1935 (Box Box 148)
  - Miscellaneous "Le-Ln", 1939 -1935 (Box Box 148)
  - Miscellaneous "La-Ld", 1935 (Box Box 148)
  - Miscellaneous "L", including some linotype news, 1936 (Box Box 148)
  - Miscellaneous "Kl-Kz", 1932 -1935 (Box Box 148)
  - Miscellaneous "K'', 1936 (Box Box 148)
  - American Express Co. - about travel and shipments, 1920 -1926 (Box Box 149)
  - Playgrounds - list of playgrounds in Roanoke, 1916 (Box Box 149)
  - Piedmont Club - announcements of meetings, dances and "smokers", 1914 (Box Box 149)
  - W. M. Pitzer (see Pocahontas C. & C. Co. 148) - about coal shipments to Stone's residence, 1911 -1920 (Box Box 149)
  - Powers of Attorney - related documents, 1930 (Box Box 149)
  - E. H. Pearl - about sale of some Borderland Coal stock, 1921 (Box Box 149)
  - Pelman Institute of America - about book offers and magazine subscriptions, 1921 (Box Box 149)
  - Ernest Peixotto - about a barrel of apples that never reached Peixotto, 1915 (Box Box 149)
  - Bills - invoices for personal goods, 1915; (2 folders) (Box Box 149)
  - Miscellaneous "K", including Kendrick-Odell Press, E. A. Kendrick, Dr. Harris E. Kirk, Kiplinger Washington Agency - about books, printing, and state of economy, 1914 -1935 (Box Box 150)
  - Mr. & Mrs. William Kearsley (Katherine & Bill) - friendly correspondence between printers, 1932 -1935 (Box Box 150)
  - Dr. Howard A. Kelly - friendly correspondence about printing, 1933 -1935 (Box Box 150)
  - Robert Kearfott - about sculptures and trays, 1933 -1935 (Box Box 150)
  - Max Mayer Maps - about printing and publishing of maps, 1921 -1931 (Box Box 150)
  - Frank Markward - about printing, 1933 (Box Box 150)
  - Hal Marchbanks - about fine printing; several samples included, 1931 -1935 (Box Box 150)
  - Miscellaneous "M" - correspondence with printing associates, 1935 -1938 (Box Box 150)
  - Magazines - about subscriptions, 1935 (Box Box 150)
  - Miscellaneous "Aa-Ad" - contain information on such diverse topics as Appalachian real estate and anti-prohibition news, 1930 -1931 (Box Box 151)
  - Miscellaneous "Ag-Am", 1930 -1931 (Box Box 151)
  - Miscellaneous "An-Az", 1930 -1931 (Box Box 151)
  - Judge C. C. Chillingworth - correspondence between these old friends about family affairs, politics, and local enterprises, 1932 -1935 (Box Box 154)
  - Christmas Card Acknowledgments - letters received thanking Stone for his specially printed Christmas card and his letters acknowledging their thanks, 1933 -1935; (2 folders) (Box Box 154)
  - Miscellaneous "D" - letters to old friends about books, personal occasions, and health; no business affairs, except an occasional response to requests from charities, 1936 -1937 (Box Box 154)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "E", 1932 -1936 (Box Box 154)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Ra-Rn" - Stone's personal correspondence with friends and associates (outside of business), 1931 -1935 (Box Box 155)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "M", 1936 (Box Box 155)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "Mo-Mz", 1931 -1937 (Box Box 155)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence "N", including some business-related material under National Assoc. of Manufacturers (newsletters, etc.), 1931 -1935 (Box Box 155)
  - Mr. Edward L. Stone - contains personal memorabilia, including photographs, love letters, and a social security card, 1902 -1920 (Box Box 155)
  - Edmund G. Gress - author of "The Art and Practice of Typography" and is a printer-friend associate of Stone's, 1922 -1935 (Box Box 156)
  - Miscellaneous "M" - about personal business (insurance, etc.) with George M. Muse, John C. Morrison, Henry F. Michell Co., C. B. Mooman, R. G. Morton, 1920 -1925 (Box Box 156)
  - Allegheny Club - social club; notices of meetings and dances, 1920 -1926 (Box Box 156)
  - Frederick Alfred - about potential business investments, 1917 -1928 (Box Box 156)
  - Miscellaneous "G" - personal business with or about Walson P. Gooch, W. A. Graut, "Gratis Fund", Walter Graham, 1921 -1927 (Box Box 156)
  - Miscellaneous "H" - personal business correspondence with Edward Hayes, Harold Coal & Coke Co., N. C. Hays, 1914 -1930 (Box Box 156)
  - Miscellaneous "B" - personal letters to old friends, written while confined to bed during a long illness, 1935 Jan -1937 Feb; (4 folders) (Box Box 157)
  - Miscellaneous "D" - personal affairs, like a dog for his daughter, forms from the Dept. of the Census, curtains at the dry cleaners, etc., 1908 -1913 (Box Box 158)
  - Dix Diamonds - catalogue of precious diamonds, no date (Box Box 158)
  - Baseball Assoc. - scorecard, schedule, and a letter telling Stone he has been made a director of the Baseball Assoc. of Roanoke that year, 1909 (Box Box 158)
  - Battle Creek Sanitarium - descriptive booklets; The Battle Creek Sanitarium was owned and operated by Dr. Kellogg, who founded the Kellogg Cereal Co., 1908 -1909 (Box Box 158)
  - Academy of Political Science - newsletters and correspondence about membership, 1929 -1932 (Box Box 159)
  - General Outdoor Advertising Co. - about their agreement to lease some land from Stone in Roanoke, 1929 -1932 (Box Box 159)
  - American Asiatic Assoc. - about subscription to their publication, 1929 -1932 (Box Box 159)
  - Louis H. Ruyl - letters to/from this artist, as well as samples of his work, 1929 -1932 (Box Box 159)
  - Old addresses - lists of names and addresses, 1929 -1932 (Box Box 159)
  - Acorns of Roanoke - about Stone's donation to this high school yearbook, 1916 (Box Box 159)
  - To Be Filed - miscellaneous personal items, 1933 (Box Box 160)
  - Christmas correspondence 1932 - translations, etc personal letters and greetings plus plans for Stone's own Christmas card (Box Box 160)
  - Miscellaneous "Mc-Md" - correspondence with personal friends and organizations, 1931 -1935 (Box Box 160)
  - Miscellaneous "Ma-Mb", 1931 -1936 (Box Box 160)
  - Martha Washington Candy Co. box covers - designs and box covers, no date (Box Box 160)
  - Peck & Peck - orders for clothing (golf socks), 1921 -1924 (Box Box 161)
  - McCaskell Investment Co. - about potential land purchases in Florida, 1924 -1926 (Box Box 161)